Finding Aid for School of Information (University of Michigan) Records 1901-2012
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Office files 1904-2001
  - 1964-1984
    - Alumnus-in-Residence (Box 11)
      - Addresses, 1969- (Box 11)
      - 1971 (Box 11)
    - Beta Phi Mu 1971-1975 (Box 11)
    - Bonk, Wallace-correspondence 1964-1968 (Box 11)
    - Budgets 1964-1979, 24 folders (Box 11)
    - Committee on Institutional Cooperation 1971-1980, 5 folders (Box 12)
      (correspondence and reports on the progress of the joint doctoral program in library science)
    - Conant Visit 1974 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum-Specialist's Degree Proposal 1964 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum-Student Questionnaire 1970 (Box 12)
    - Curriculum Committee 1968-1975, 5 folders (Box 12)
      (includes committee minutes, correspondence, memos, and notes)
    - Doctoral Program
      - Admitted-did not come (Box 13)
      - Committee of the Doctoral Program (Box 13)
      - Directory of Doctoral Students (C.I.C. Schools) (Box 13)
      - Doctoral examinations 1955-1961, 1973 (Box 13)
      - Doctoral Library Schools Research Group (Box 13)
      - Doctoral Program-changes (Box 13)
      - Doctoral Program-Marco Study 1966 (Box 13)
      - Doctoral Program-statistics (Box 13)
      - Doctoral students-communications (Box 13)
      - Enrollment control (Box 13)
      - Michigan Ph.D.'s questionnaire-replies (Box 13)
      - Milestone roster of candidates (Box 13)
      - Newsletter "Doctoral Students Memo", 1974-75 (Box 13)
      - Ph.D. Program-general 1964-1971 (Box 13)
      - Policy statement on inactive Ph.D. students 1967 (Box 13)
      - Questions in cataloging (Box 13)
      - Screening procedures (Box 13)
      - Statistics for Schick's ALA report (Box 13)
    - Enrollment Trends, early 1970s (Box 13)
    - Extension Courses (paper by Rosemary Magrill) circa 1970 (Box 13)
    - Field Experience (materials regarding placement of students in libraries for field training) 1973-1981 (Box 13)
    - Graduate Employees Organization, collected materials 1974-1975, 5 folders (Box 13)
    - Knapp Project 1971-1973
      - Advisory Board (Box 13)
      - Budget (Box 13)
      - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Evaluation and Research (Box 13)
      - Final Report (Box 13)
    - Knapp Project
      - First Year Interim Report (Box 13)
      - Original Grant Proposal (Box 13)
      - Student Meetings (Box 13)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 13)
    - Library Schools
      - Correspondence (with other library schools) 1961-1970 (Box 14)
      - Peer Review Study 1974-1975 (Box 14)
      - White Questionnaire (ranking library schools) 1980 (Box 14)
    - Library System Planning Committee 1970-1971 (Box 14)
    - Long-Range Planning Committee 1967-1977, 4 folders (Box 14)
    - Michigan Historical Collections 1970-1974 (Box 14)
      (correspondence regarding his service on the Executive Board)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
    - North Campus General Library and Library School Expansion Plans (includes "Summary Prospectus") 1973-1975 (Box 14)
    - Placement 1972 Study (Box 14)
    - Policy Compilation (by the university) 1974 (Box 14)
    - School Status
      - Bonk's statement to Haber 1964 (Box 14)
      - Correspondence 1963-1972 (Box 14)
      - Documents provided to the panel 1967 (Box 14)
    - Skipper Proposal (on visiting professors) 1977 (Box 14)
    - Speakers
      - Convocation speakers 1968-1974 (Box 14)
      - Foley, Dermot 1973 (Box 14)
    - Specialists Program 1966-1974 (Box 14)
    - Students-Library Science Student Organization 1972-1974 (Box 14)
      (includes LSSO constitution and newsletters)
    - Vainstein, Rose 1980 (Box 14)
      (day in honor of; includes letters and booklet in tribute to Vainstein)
    - Vance, Kenneth 1981 (Box 14)
      (day in honor of; letters written to Vance on the occasion of his retirement)
    - Workshops
      - 1964 School Library Planning (Box 14)
      - 1965 Public Relations and the School Library (Box 14)
      - 1966 Selection, Organization, and Use of Newer Educational Media (Box 14)
      - 1967 The Materials Center in an Elementary School (Box 14)
      - 1967 Supervision of School Libraries (Box 14)
      - 1968 The Junior High School (Box 14)
      - 1969 Production of Instructional Materials (Grand Rapids) (Box 14)
      - 1969 Production of Instructional Media (Box 14)
      - 1970 Production of Instructional Media (Box 14)
      - 1971 Improving Communication Skills of School Library Media Specialists (Box 14)
      - 1972 Media for Multi-ethnic Understanding (Box 14)
      - 1973 Kids and Books (Traverse City) (Box 14)
      - 1976 Creative Problem-Solving for Media Specialists in Times of Financial Adversity (Box 14)
      - 1977 Creative Programming for School Media Center (Box 14)
      - 1978 Issues in Library Media Management (Box 14)
      - 1980 Update on Technology for School Library Media Specialists (Box 14)
      - "Evaluating Workshops Conducted by the School of Library Science, the University of Michigan," thesis by Gertrude Lowe Carlstrom 1970 (Box 14)
  - 1930-1994
    The Office Files, 1930-1994 subseries (9.5 linear feet) is arranged alphabetically by folder heading and then chronologically. The records in this series reflect the activities of the school. Many of the files continue previous subjects and complement the records in earlier accessions. The Accreditation files continue from the previous accession. These files provide information on the activities of the school, the curriculum, and the faculty from year to year.
    The Council on Library Resources (CLR) files and the Title II B files both provide information on two programs for educating and training future librarians. The CLR program focused specifically on coursework and training for students that would provide them with the background necessary for working in a college or research library. The Title II B program provided opportunities for training for minority students.
    The Curriculum files provide information on the courses being taught at the school and requirements for certain specialties. Types of materials found in these files include course descriptions, syllabi, and course materials, such as assignments and handouts. Also included in these files are materials on the curriculum for a School Library Media Specialist concentration. The Statistics files provide information on students, faculty and the school itself. Much of the information in these files complements that found in Dean Bidlack's files.
    - Academic Affairs 1985-1990 (Box 22)
    - Accreditation
      - ALA Committee on Accreditation
        - "Report on the School of Library Science of the University of Michigan" 1983, 2 volumes (Box 22)
        - Site Visit 1982/83 (Box 22)
      - Annual Report to ALA Committee on Accreditation
        - 1977/78 (Box 23)
        - 1979/80 (Box 23)
        - 1980/81 (Box 23)
        - 1980/81 Faculty Questionnaire (Box 23)
        - 1982/83-1987/88, 6 folders (Box 23)
      - Self-Study Report
        - 1974, 2 volumes (Box 23)
        - 1982, 2 volumes (Box 23)
        - 1989, 2 volumes (Box 23)
    - Admissions 1984 (Box 24)
    - Affirmative Action
      - 1975-1991 (Box 24)
      - Institutional Analysis Survey 1976, 1979 (Box 24)
      - Minorities 1966-1975 (Box 24)
      - Student Statistics 1969/70-1980/81 (Box 24)
      - Survey of Other Universities 1976 (Box 24)
      - Women 1970/71-1972/73, 1977 (Box 24)
    - Alumnae Athena Award 1973-1975 (Box 24)
    - Alumni-in-Residence 1969-1984, 14 folders (Box 24)
    - Alumni Directory (Classes of 1927 to 1951), 1976 (Box 24)
    - Alumni Society (Library School) 1930-1992
      - Alumni Census 1983-1986 (Box 24)
      - Alumni Directory (1927-1951) 1976 (Box 24)
      - Alumni Reunions 1978-1992 (Box 24)
      - Constitutions 1938-1984 (Box 24)
      - Correspondence 1930-1985, 3 folders (Box 24)
      - Executive Board Minutes 1949-1966, 1991 (Box 24)
      - Fundraising 1976-1981 (Box 24)
      - List of Officers (Box 24)
      - Reports to University of Michigan Alumni Society 1976-1992 (Box 24)
    - American Library Association (ALA)
      - 1972-1973, 1977, 1979 (Box 24)
      - 1986-1992 (Box 24)
      - Goals Award (Students to Dallas) 1970 (Box 24)
    - Association of American Library Schools (AALS)
      - 1952-1963, 5 folders (Box 24)
      - 1964-1972, 1975-1982 (Box 24)
      - Report to AALS 1978/79-1981/82, 4 folders (Box 25)
    - Beta Phi Mu 1954-1991 (Box 25)
    - Budget
      - 1981/82-1985/86, 1990/91, 5 folders (Box 25)
      - Requests for Programs 1971/72-1975/76 (Box 25)
    - Center for Research on Learning and Teaching
      - Faculty Proposals 1976-1977 (Box 25)
    - Children's Book Collection 1979 (Box 25)
    - Columbia University Preservation Program, SILS Visit 1991 (Box 25)
    - Commencement
      - Faculty Participants 1969-1984 (Box 25)
      - SILS Recognition Ceremony 1990 (Box 25)
    - Committees
      - Curriculum Committee 1979/80-1980/81 (Box 25)
      - Faculty-Student Memberships 1968/69-1983/84 (Box 25)
    - Computing
      - 1969/70-1972/73, 1977/78-1978/79 (Box 25)
      - 1981/82-1984/85, 2 folders (Box 25)
      - SILS Computer Usage 1976-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 25)
    - Consultants, Holley and Buckland Report 1983 (Box 25)
    - Continuing Education
      - Committee on Professional Development 1971-1973 (Box 25)
      - Correspondence 1981-1984 (Box 25)
      - Grant Proposals and Budget 1981-1983 (Box 25)
      - SILS Course Offerings 1978-1984 (Box 25)
    - Convocations
      - 1964/65, 1968/69, 1970, 1975 (Box 25)
      - Flyers 1977, 1990-1994 (Box 25)
      - Placement Talk undated (Box 25)
    - Council on Library Resources Professional Education for Academic Research Librarians Grant
      - Admissions and Curriculum (Box 26)
      - Correspondence 1980-1985, 4 folders (Box 26)
      - Course Syllabi (Box 26)
      - Financial 1981-1983 (Box 26)
      - Internship Seminar 1983-1985 (Box 26)
      - Internships
        - 1981-1983 (Box 26)
        - Students A-Z 1983-1986, 4 folders (Box 32)
          [SR Restricted until Jan. 1, 2061 ]
        - Student Final Reports 1983-1985, 4 folders (Box 32)
          [SR Restricted until Jan. 1, 2060 ]
      - Program Description and Publicity (Box 26)
      - Program Evaluation 1985-1986 (Box 26)
      - Proposal 1980 (Box 26)
      - SILS Committee on Education for Research Librarians
        - 1980 (Box 26)
        - Planning 1980-1981 (Box 33)
    - Court Case (Riener v. Bidlack)
      [RESTRICTED]
      - Court Documents
        - 1975, 2 folders (Box 33)
        - 1978-1984, 1987, 7 folders (Box 33)
      - Supporting Documents
        - 1961-1974, 10 folders (Box 33)
        - 1976 (Box 33)
    - Curriculum
      - L.S. 503 Music Bibliography (Box 26)
      - L.S. 517/521/529 Integrated Core Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. Building Library Collections, Summer and Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 526 Technologies for Information Management (Box 26)
      - L.S. 521 Collection Development and Management Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 529 General Reference Materials and Services (Box 26)
      - L.S. 565 Literature for Children Fall 1986 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 547 History of Books and Printing (Box 26)
      - L.S. 550 Introduction to Information Science Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 570 Literature for Young Adults Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 576 Administration of the School Library Media Program 1980/81, Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 607 Evaluation of Library Services, Summer 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 608 International Librarianship Fall 1991 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 615 Reading Interests of Adults Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 620 Sources of Information in the Social Sciences (Slavens) (Box 26)
      - L.S. 620 Sources of Information in the Social Sciences (Taylor), Summer 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 623 Sources of Info. in Science and Technology Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 626 Sources of Info. in the Humanities (Box 26)
      - L.S. 631 Sources of Info. in the Fine Arts (Box 26)
      - L.S. 635 Sources of Legal Information Spring 1992 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 636 Contemporary Library Developments Summer-Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 637 Problems in the Administration of Archives Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 644 Photographic Communication (Box 26)
      - L.S. 661 Programming and Software Design for Information Processing (Box 26)
      - L.S. 665 Design of Bibliographic Data Base Systems Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 686 Storytelling Summer 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 690 Directed Field Experience (Box 26)
      - L.S. 700 Seminar in School Library Media Problems (Box 26)
      - L.S. 703 Seminar in Media for Children and Young Adults (Box 26)
      - L.S. 723 Public Library Services (Box 26)
      - L.S. 727 Administration of Archives Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 738 Special Libraries (Box 26)
      - L.S. 750 Seminar in Music Librarianship Winter 1983 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 760 Seminar in University Library Administration Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 762 Library Buildings and Equipment (Box 26)
      - L.S. 765 International Information Policy Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - L.S. 813 Seminar on Trends and Issues in Librarianship Fall 1982 (Box 26)
      - Complaints 1991 (Box 26)
      - Course Descriptions and Syllabi 1991 (Box 26)
      - Course Evaluations 1970-1976, 1989 (Box 26)
      - Course Offerings 1983/84-1984/85 (Box 26)
      - Courses Taught by Faculty 1976/77-1984/85 (Box 26)
      - Mini Courses 1980-1985 (Box 26)
      - Prison Library Course 1973/74 (Box 26)
      - SILS Core Curriculum Task Force Report 1994 (Box 26)
      - School Library Media Specialist
        - 1981-1985 (Box 26)
        - Directed Field Experience Student Journals Winter 1992 (Box 32)
          [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2067 ]
    - Dean Search 1992 (Box 26)
    - Directories 1976, 1979 (Box 26)
    - Doctoral Students
      - Doctoral Students Organization, Correspondence 1979-1981, 1990 (Box 26)
      - Grievance 1985/86, 3 folders (Box 32)
        [SR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2061 ]
      - Policies and Procedures 1976-1980 (Box 26)
      - Statistics 1964/65-1977/78 (Box 26)
      - Student Lists 1953-1982 (Box 26)
      - Thesis and Dissertation Abstracts 1978-1982 (Box 26)
    - "The Eclectic" (Student Publication) 1979 (Box 27)
    - Enrollment, 1975-1977, 1985 (Box 27)
    - Equipment
      - Equipment Requests 1985/86 (Box 27)
      - Inventories 1951, 1971/72, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Extension Program
      - Courses Offered 1966/67-1981/82, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - Planning 1981/82-1983/84 (Box 27)
      - Statistics 1968/69-1982/83 (Box 27)
    - Faculty
      - Appointments 1990 (Box 27)
      - Meetings 1991-1992 (Box 27)
      - Retreat November 1990, January 1991 (Box 27)
    - Faculty Search
      - Associate Dean Search 1986/87 (Box 27)
      - Candidates A-Z 1986/87, 4 folders (Box 32)
      - Faculty Comments 1986-1989, 1 folders (Box 27)
      - Faculty Comments 1986-1989, 1 folders (Box 32)
      - Interviews
        - 1987/88 (Box 32)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July 1, 2016 ]
        - 1988/89 (Box 32)
          [PR RESTRICTED until July ,1 2019 ]
      - Search Committee 1987/88-1988/89 (Box 27)
    - Financial Aid
      - Policies 1980, 1984/85-1985/86 (Box 27)
      - Scholarships
        - 1969/70 (Box 27)
        - 1974/75-1984/85, 2 folders (Box 27)
        - De La Vergne Scholarship Fund 1989 (Box 27)
      - SILS Student Loan Fund 1973/74-1978/79 (Box 27)
      - Task Force on Graduate Student Aid 1981/82 (Box 27)
    - Foreign Students 1927-1974 (Box 27)
    - Foundations
      - H.W. Wilson Foundation, Application for Continuation of CLR Grant 1984 (Box 27)
      - Mellon Foundation, Residency Program 1983 (Box 27)
    - Graduate School (Rackham) Correspondence 1964-1983 (Box 27)
    - Historic Documents (Xeroxes) 1909-1992 (Box 27)
    - Information and Library Studies Student Association (ILSSA), Minutes, Annual Reports, Correspondence 1989-1990 (Box 27)
    - Information Technology General Council 1987/88-1993/94 (Box 27)
    - Instructional Strategy Services/Instructional, Research, and Information Service (ISS/IRIS)
      - Correspondence 1978-1992, 4 folders (Box 27)
      - ISS Review 1985 (Box 27)
      - Library Science and Information Management Software 1987 (Box 27)
      - Media Facilities Proposal (Hessler) 1979 (Box 27)
      - Microcomputer Lab 1983/84 (Box 27)
      - SILS Support 1986/87-1992/93 (Box 27)
      - SILS Usage 1987/88, 1991/92-1992/93 (Box 27)
      - Staff Meeting Minutes 1979-1980 (Box 27)
    - Instructional Technologies Division 1990-1991 (Box 27)
    - International Federation of Library Associations 1985, 1991, 1993 (Box 27)
    - International Year of the Child, Programming 1979 (Box 27)
    - Internships
      - County Library Internship 1942 (Box 27)
    - Issues and Challenges of the 1980s Gale Research Grant, 1981 (Box 27)
    - Lecturers
      - Guest Lecturers, Correspondence 1950-1969, 2 folders (Box 27)
      - John Cotton Dana Lecture 1967 (Box 27)
    - Library Associates Program
      - Correspondence 1990-1991 (Box 28)
      - Proposals 1982, 1985 (Box 28)
      - Report of SILS Associate Program 1993 (Box 28)
    - Library of Congress
      - Correspondence 1938-1974 (scattered dates) (Box 28)
      - Internship Program 1951-1984, 1987 (Box 28)
    - Library School Program, Bonk Memo to Haber 1965 (Box 28)
    - Library Science Library 1978, 1990 (Box 28)
    - McHale Memorial Book Fund 1951-1972 (scattered dates) (Box 28)
    - Medical Librarianship 1956-1972 (scattered dates) (Box 28)
    - Medical Library Association, Correspondence 1949-1978 (scattered dates) (Box 28)
    - Memorandum of Understanding (SILS and OAA) 1978 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Association of Library Schools 1953-1965 (scattered dates) (Box 28)
    - Michigan Historical Collections 1970, 1974, 1980 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Interorganization Council on Continuing Library Education (MICCLE) 1977-1980 (Box 28)
    - Michigan Library Association 1962-1963, 1970-1974, 1977, 1980 (Box 28)
    - Michigan State Department of Education 1968-1971 (Box 28)
    - Michigan State Library, Scholarships 1960, 1968-1969 (Box 28)
    - MTS Electronic Conference 1986 (Box 28)
    - News Releases 1964-1984, 1990-1992, 5 folders (Box 28)
    - Online Searching Lab, J. Weedman Proposal 1986 (Box 28)
    - Peer Institutions 1987 (Box 28)
    - Personnel 1982, 1984-1985 (Box 28)
    - Phi Kappa Phi 1936, 1942-1966 (Box 28)
    - Pi Lambda Theta 1946-1966, 1972 (Box 28)
    - Placement Service 1959-1964, 1971-1972, 1986 (Box 28)
    - Placement Statistics 1959-1967 (Box 28)
    - Planning 1989, 1991 (Box 28)
    - President's Office
      - Fleming 1969-1979, 1989 (Box 28)
      - Shapiro 1980-1981 (Box 28)
    - Promotion and Tenure Survey 1980 (Box 28)
    - Quarters
      - 1928, 1943, 1954, 1960-1968, 1973 (Box 28)
      - Faculty-Student Lounge 1972 (Box 28)
    - Receptions 1968-1970 (Box 28)
    - Registration, Course Tally Sheets 1969/70-1983/84 (Box 28)
    - Research Assistant Requests 1984/85-1985/86 (Box 28)
    - Residency Program (Dougherty Proposal) 1983 (Box 28)
    - Scheduling 1976-1983, 1990, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Scholar-in-Residence
      - Dermot Foley 1983 (Box 29)
      - K.C. Harrison 1970-1972 (Box 29)
      - Frank Hogg 1979-1980 (Box 29)
    - School Policies 1969-1983, 2 folders (Box 29)
    - Science Research Associates, Inc. 1961, 1970-1973 (Box 29)
    - SILS Advisory Committee Meeting Minutes November 16, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Special Libraries Association 1946-1973, 1977-1978 (Box 29)
    - Special Libraries Association, Michigan Chapter 1964-1965, 1968, 1974, 1987 (Box 29)
    - Special Libraries Institute, 1971-972; 1976 (Box 29)
    - State and Community Relations, Office of 1981 (Box 29)
    - Statistics
      - American Association of Library Schools Enrollment Survey 1943-1967 (Box 29)
      - Faculty Grade Distribution 1970/71-1983/84 (Box 29)
      - Graduates-Women and Minorities 1976-1979 (Box 29)
      - Library Journal Placement Survey, 1973-1975, 1977-1979 (Box 29)
      - Minority Enrollment Survey 1973 (Box 29)
      - Minority Students 1972-1980 (Box 29)
      - Peer Review-Lelong Study 1977 (Box 29)
      - Student Ages 1975, 1977 (Box 29)
      - Student Credit Hours per Faculty Member 1976/77-1983/84 (Box 29)
      - Surveys 1967/68, 1970-1982 (Box 29)
    - Summer Sessions
      - Institutes 1969 (Box 29)
      - Workshops 1964, 1967, 1969, 1971 (Box 29)
    - Surveys 1984 (Box 29)
    - Technology Committee 1981, 1991 (Box 29)
    - Title II B
      - General Correspondence 1969-1972 (Box 29)
      - Hessler Testimony to Ford Committee 1979 (Box 29)
      - Letters of Support to Congress 1969-1970, 1978-1979, 4 folders (Box 29)
      - Library Fellowship Study Questionnaire 1969 (Box 29)
      - Library Training Institute Proposal 1971/72 (Box 29)
      - Library Training Program
        - 1978, 1980-1991, 2 folders (Box 29)
        - Analysis 1975, 1978 (Box 29)
        - Correspondence 1965/66 (Box 29)
        - Grant Application Materials 1966/67, 1968/69-1971/72, 4 folders (Box 29)
        - Performance Reports 1977/78, 1980/81-1985/86 (Box 29)
    - Title IX, School's Compliance Documents 1976 (Box 30)
    - University Committee on International Academic Affairs 1992 (Box 30)
    - University Microfilms Xerox 1973 (Box 30)
    - University Relations and Development Office 1971-1979 (Box 30)
    - University Seminars 1989 (Box 30)
    - University Senate
      - Librarian Membership 1968-1993, 3 folders (Box 30)
      - Senate Advisory Committee on University Affairs (SACUA) 1986-1987 (Box 30)
      - Senate Assembly, Librarian Membership 1969-1984 (Box 30)
    - Vernon Tate Collection 1983-1985 (Box 30)
    - Vice President for Academic Affairs, Correspondence 1968/69-1970/71, 1975/76-1983/84, 4 folders (Box 30)
    - Vice President for Research, Correspondence 1977, 1979, 1981 (Box 30)
    - Visitors 1950-1965, 1976, 1984, 1991, 2 folders (Box 30)
    - Wayne State University Library Science Program 1985 (Box 30)
    - Western Michigan University Credit Transfer 1983 (Box 30)
    - Wilson, H. W. Company 1938, 1940, 1947-1948, 1951, 1953, 1967 (Box 30)
    - Workshops 1970, 1978 (Box 30)
  - 1969-2001
    The Office Files, 1969-2001 subseries is arranged alphabetically and covers a period from 1969 to 2001. The series is particularly rich in the documentation of the discussion and changes pertaining to the school's curriculum. The series includes meeting minutes and notes of the curriculum committee from 1969 to 1990 as well as minutes from the Curriculum Task Force (1992-1995). A group of 5.25" computer disks that are mainly unlabeled and not dated are located in boxes 42 and 43.
    - Academic Program Information, (scattered dates) (Box 38)
    - American Library Association Accreditation Process
      - Back-up Materials for Self-Study Accreditation (1989-1996) (Box 38)
      - Committee on Accreditation (1983-1988) (Box 38)
      - Committee on Accreditation 1998 (Box 38)
      - Report on the School of Library Science June 1983 (Box 38)
      - Self-Study Correspondence 1988-1989 (Box 38)
      - Self Study Report, Volume I November 1989 (Box 38)
      - Self-Study Report, Volume II November 1989 (Box 38)
      - Self Study Visit, Correspondence and Notes 1989 (Box 38)
    - Admissions Information Packet 2000-2001 (Box 38)
    - Annual Report 1969-1970 (Box 38)
    - Atkins, Dean (Daniel E.), correspondence (early 1990s) (Box 38)
    - Atkins, Dean (Daniel E.), miscellaneous papers 1992 (Box 38)
    - Budget Conference materials 1985 (Box 39)
    - Building planning discussions 1985-1989 (Box 39)
    - Calendar of Activities 1970-1985 (Box 39)
    - Coordinating Committee for Strategic Planning 1984-1985 (Box 39)